Now that you've trained your estimator on some formatted train data,
使用特殊格式的训练数据训练了 estimator 后
the next thing you should have done is deploy your model to create a linear predictor.
下一步是部署模型来创建线性预测器
This just requires that you pass in
只需传入关于
some information about the instance type you want for deployment.
要部署的实例类型的信息
In this case, I'm using a T2 medium instance.
我将使用 t2.medium 实例
This is a good default for these exercises
这个默认实例对于这些练习
and when working in a development environment in general.
以及一般的开发环境来说足够了
So after about seven minutes,
大约 7 分钟后
a call to deploy creates both a model and an endpoint with some name.
调用 deploy 将创建模型和具有某个名称的端点
Now, I have a predictor endpoint that I can use to make predictions on my test data.
我可以使用该预测器端点对测试数据进行预测
Let's do a simple test first.
先简单测试下
I took a look at the predictor information here and I can see that
看看这里的预测器信息
the LinearLeanerPredictor requires a numpy and ndarry as input,
可以看出 LinearLeanerPredictor 需要一个 numpy ndarry 作为输入
and returns a list of record objects,
并返回 record 对象列表
one record for each data point in the input array.
输入数组中的每个数据点对应一条记录
So here, I'm converting our test features into a numpy array,
在这里将测试特征转换成 numpy 数组
and I'm just going to pass in the first row of
我将传入第一行数据
data and see what our linear predictor returns.
看看线性预测器会返回什么
I can see that for this one data point,
对于这一个数据点
I have a predicted label,
返回了预测标签
let's hope in value float 32 tensor.
值存储为 float32_tensor.
I get the label 0,
标签为 0
which I know corresponds to a valid transaction.
对应于有效交易
In addition to a predicted label,
除了预测的标签之外
I also get a score which gives me a more precise value if I need it.
还可以查看这个分数 它可以告诉我更精确的值
The score is what's rounded to the predicted label and so the score
分数会四舍五入为预测标签
gives me a better idea of how confident the model is in its predicted label.
所以分数可以更清晰地告诉我模型在预测标签时的自信程度
In this case, a value really close to zero indicates that it's pretty
在此例中 很接近 0 的值表示模型
confident that the past end datapoint is indeed a valid transaction.
非常确信传入的数据点的确是有效交易
A higher value here, closer to 0.05,
接近 0.05 的更高值表示
would indicate a lot of uncertainty in the prediction.
模型在预测时不确定性很大
So using what I know about this record format,
根据我对这个记录格式的了解
I've created the helper function below.
我在下面创建了辅助函数
Evaluate takes in a deployed predictor,
evaluate 的参数包括部署的预测器
some test features and labels,
测试特征和标签
and then it returns a variety of metrics.
然后返回各种指标
The first line of code in here is just me dividing
第一行代码
my test data into batches because there's a lot of it.
会将测试数据分成批次 因为数据很多
Getting predictions for each batch calling predictor.predict over batch.
通过调用 predictor.predict(batch) 获得每个批次的预测
These batches are going to be over a 100 data points each.
这些批次每个有 100 个以上的数据点
Then for each batch in my production batches,
对于 prediction_batches 中的每个批次
I'm going to get a pointer to each point in that batch
我将获得该批次中每个数据点的指针
and get the predicted label calling x-dot label.
并通过调用 x.label 获得预测的标签
Then I'm just concatenating all of those results to get our test predictions.
然后将所有这些结果连接到一切 获得测试预测
Finally, I'm doing a series of comparison between
最后比较生成的测试预测
our generated test predictions and our true class labels.
与真实类别标签
I'm calculating the number of true positives,
计算真正例 假正例
false positives, true negatives, and false negatives.
真负例和假负例的数量
Then from those, calculating
然后根据这些数量
binary classification metrics for our test data including recall,
计算测试数据的二元分类指标
precision, and total accuracy.
包括召回率 精确率和总准确率
I have an argument verbose,
这里有个 verbose 参数
that is by default set to true which will print out these three metrics here.
默认设为 true 这时候将输出所有这三个指标
So next, I'm running this code and seeing how our linear predictor performs.
接下来运行此代码 看看线性预测器的效果
I'm passing in the predictor,
传入预测器
our formatted test features or test labels and I'm setting for both to be true,
特殊格式的测试特征和测试标签 并将 verbose 设为 true
which means we'll print out the metrics I'm interested in.
表示输出我感兴趣的指标
When I run this, the first thing I see is that I get
运行此代码后 首先看到
a really high accuracy, 99.9 percent.
准确率非常高 达到 99.9%
But let's look at this table of data.
看看这个表格数据
So the rows are our true actual labels,
行表示真实标签
zero for valid and one for fraudulent.
0 表示有效交易 1 表示欺诈性交易
Our columns are the predicted labels.
列是预测标签
So the values here indicate the number of test points that are
这个值表示正确分类为有效交易的
classified correctly as valid and here,
测试数据点的数量
the number I correctly classified as fraudulent.
这个值表示正确分类为欺诈性交易的数量
But I can also see that for 33 of my truly valid cases,
但是还看到有 33 个真实有效交易
I misclassified them as fraudulent and for our fraudulent cases,
被错误地分类成欺诈性交易
32 of them were misclassified as valid.
在欺诈性交易中 有32 个错误地分类成有效交易
That's what's making our values for recall and
所以召回率和精确率的值
precision much lower than the accuracy value.
比准确率的值低了很多
So even with a high accuracy,
即使准确率很高
there is still room to improve this model.
模型依然有改进的空间
But now, I'm done evaluating this model and it's
现在我已经评估完模型
good practice to always delete the endpoint once you're done with evaluation.
养成良好习惯 在评估完后始终记得删除端点
So here, I have a helper function that accepts
在这里有个辅助函数
a predictor as end point and then deletes an endpoint by name.
它将接受预测器的端点并根据名称删除端点
I'm calling it here and I should see that my endpoint is deleted.
在这里调用该辅助函数 应该会看到端点删除了
Next, I'll discuss ways we might improve upon this model,
接下来 我们将讨论如何改进此模型
including managing class imbalance in the training set
包括解决训练集的类别不平衡性问题
and tuning this model according to goals we have as developers.
并根据开发目标优化此模型